Josue Alexis Salgado Romero

+52 5519312174

l4jasr@gmail.com



Ciudad de México, México



codepen.io/princesspoteto/



github.com/PrincessPoteto https://www.linkedin.com/in/ josue-alexis-scd/

LANGUAGES:

English: A2 CEFR

Spanish: Native



Web developer with one and ahalf years of experience. My focus in the last year has been Cloud Computing, and support, so I seek to have interventions in Teams/Projects where I can improve my skills, learn, share and help others. My goal is to provide solutions to teams and continue specializing.

SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

HARD SKILLS:

- Amazon S3
- Amazon EC2
- AWS IAM
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Python
- SQL

SOFT SKILLS:

- Teamwork
- Empaty
- Listening skills
- Work ethic
- Taking Responsability

EXPERIENCE

May 2021 - July 2022 CDMX. México

WEB DEVELOPER

Tecnoemprendimiento

- Collaborated with the team to design, structure, and implement new websites and update existing.
- Developed and structure client websites, ensuring that all needs were met and company policies.
- Collaborated with project manager and designer team.

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 CDMX. México

COLLEGE PROFESSOR (Operating Systems, Network Fundamentals, and Database Administration)

Universidad UEM

- Evaluated the students individually to identify areas of difficulties.
- Guide students in using technology to database manage.
- Taught students the use of Cisco Packet Tracer.
- Lectured, written tests quizzes, powerpoint presentations, graded exams and update teachings materials with the latest information available.

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 CDMX. México

TECHNICAL SUPPORT (Help Desk and inventory management) TSJCDMX (Superior Court of Justice, Mexico City)

- Process and successful resolved a high income of trouble tickets via phone, remote or on site technical support.
- Proficiency with networking and understand concepts such as VPN, DHCP, DNS, IPv4, Ip Subnets, routing, switching, and firewalls.
- Perform test on computer equipment and programs.

EDUCATION

July 11, 2022

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

AWS training and certification

AWS re/Start Graduated Bootcamp INSTITUTE / AWS

Bachelor of Computer Science

Universidad Latina

Aug 2016 - Jun 2020

Apr 2022 – Jul 2022